/*
 * To change this license header, choose License Headers in Project Properties.
 * To change this template file, choose Tools | Templates
 * and open the template in the editor.
 */
import java.util.ArrayList;

/**
 *
 * @author Fleshgod4618
 */
public abstract class Human {

    public abstract void open();

    public abstract void setCards(ArrayList<Integer> cards);

    public abstract boolean checkSum();

    ArrayList<Integer> mycards;

}
